A Guide to the American Conservation Association (ACA) records FA475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Files, 1
  - Grant Files, 1982-1986; 1.3
    - Friends of the Earth Foundation (Box 61)
    - Human Enviromnent Center (Box 61)
    - Lamb, George R. (Box 61)
    - Landscape Architecture Foundation (Box 62)
    - The Meditation Institute (Box 62)
    - Minutes/Meetings, 1985-1987 (Box 62)
    - Minutes/Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 62)
    - Minutes/Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 62)
    - Mohonk Preserve, Inc. (Box 62)
    - John Muir Institute for Urban Wildlife (Box 62)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association (Box 62)
    - National Wildflower Research Center (Box 62)
    - National Wildlife Federation (NWF) (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1986 (Box 62)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1982-1985 (Box 62)
    - New York-New Jersey Trial Conference (Box 63)
    - New York State Natural Heritage Trust (Box 63)
    - Northeast New York Public Telecommunication Council Inc. (Box 63)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 63)
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 63)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts (Box 63)
    - Project for Public Spaces (Box 63)
    - Regional Plan Association (Box 63)
    - Review and Planning Committee (Box 63)
    - Save the Redwoods League (Box 64)
    - Scenic Hudson Inc. (Box 64)
    - Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund Inc. (Box 64)
    - Southern Environmental Law Center (Box 64)
    - The Student Conservation Association (Box 64)
    - Thorne Ecological Institute (Box 64)
    - Whyte, William H. (Box 64)
    - The Wilderness Society (Box 64)
  - Grant Files, 1987-1991; 1.4
    - A-Z, 1987-1991 (Box 65)
    - The Adirondack Council, 3 folders. (Box 65)
    - Academy of Natural Sciences, 1987-1990 (Box 65)
    - The Adirondack Land Trust, Inc. (Box 65)
    - Adirondack Nature Conservancy (Box 65)
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation (Box 65)
    - American Farmland Trust (Box 65)
    - American Littoral Society (Box 66)
    - American Rivers Inc., 2 folders. (Box 66)
    - American Society for the Protection of Nature in Israel (Box 66)
    - Americans for the Environment (Box 66)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 66)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 66)
    - Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, 2 folders. (Box 66)
    - Clean Water Fund (Box 66)
    - Coalition for Scenic Beauty (Box 66)
    - Coast Alliance, 2 folders. (Box 66)
    - The Conservation Foundation (Box 67)
    - The Conservation Fund (Box 67)
    - Conservation Law Foundation of New England (Box 67)
    - Earth Day - Partner's for the Planet Databank (Box 67)
    - Earth Day International (Box 67)
    - Earth Day 1990 (Box 67)
    - Eco Fund 1992 (Box 67)
    - Environmental Law Institute (Box 67)
    - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 67)
    - Environmental Policy Institute, 3 folders. (Box 67)
    - Finances (Box 68)
    - Foresight Films (Box 68)
    - Friends of the Earth Foundation (Box 68)
    - Friends of Shawangunks (Box 68)
    - Grand Canyon Trust (Box 68)
    - Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 68)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway Council (Box 68)
    - Inform, 2 folders. (Box 68)
    - International Council for Bird Preservation/ United States Section, Inc. (Box 68)
    - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning (Box 68)
    - The Land Trust Alliance (Box 68)
    - Land Trust Exchange (Box 68)
    - Land and Water Fund of the Rockies (Box 69)
    - Lighthawk, the Wings of Conservation (Box 69)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 69)
    - Manomet Bird Conservancy (Box 69)
    - Meetings, 1991; 2 folders. (Box 69)
    - Meetings, 1990 (Box 69)
    - Meetings, 1989 (Box 69)
    - Meetings, 1988 (Box 69)
    - Meetings - Mineral Policy Center, 1987 (Box 69)
    - Montana Land Reliance (Box 69)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 70)
    - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 2 folders. (Box 70)
    - National Institute for Urban Wildlife (Box 70)
    - National Park Foundation (Box 70)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association, 3 folders. (Box 70)
    - National Wildflower Research Center (Box 70)
    - National Wildlife Federation, 2 folders. (Box 70)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2 folders. (Box 71)
    - Nature Conservancy (Box 71)
    - Nature Conservancy of Hawaii (Box 71)
    - New Renaissance Center (Box 71)
    - New York Environmental Institute Inc. (Box 71)
    - New York Parks and Conservation Association (Box 71)
    - New York State Natural Heritage Trust (Box 71)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 72)
    - Northern Rockies Action Group (Box 72)
    - 1000 Friends of Florida, 2 folders. (Box 72)
    - 1000 Friends of Oregon (Box 72)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 72)
    - Roger Troy Peterson Institute of Natural History (Box 72)
    - Project for Public Spaces, 2 folders. (Box 72)
    - Rails to Trails Conservancy, 2 folders. (Box 73)
    - Regional Plan Association (Box 73)
    - Renew America Inc. (Box 73)
    - River Watch Network (Box 73)
    - Scenic America, 2 folders. (Box 73)
    - Scenic America - Billboard Editorials, 1987-1988 (Box 73)
    - Scenic Hudson, 3 folders. (Box 74)
    - Shawangunks Conservancy, Inc. (Box 74)
    - Sierra Club Foundation & Legal Defense Fund, 2 folders. (Box 74)
    - Snake River Institute (Box 74)
    - Southeast Alaska Conservation Council (Box 74)
    - Southern Environmental Law Center (Box 74)
    - Student Conservation Association (Box 75)
    - Thorne Ecological Institute (Box 75)
    - Tides Foundation (Box 75)
    - Trust for Public Land, 2 folders. (Box 75)
    - Trustees for Alaska (Box 75)
    - United States Government - President's Commission on the American Outdoors (Box 75)
    - University of Washington, Seattle WA (Box 75)
    - Vermont Natural Resources Council, 2 folders. (Box 75)
    - The Walkways Center, Folder and binder. (Box 75)
    - The Izaak Walton League of America (Box 76)
    - The Westchester Land Trust (Box 76)
    - Wilderness Society, 4 folders. (Box 76)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 76)
    - World Wildlife Fund (WWF) (Box 76)
    - Wyoming Outdoor Council (Box 76)
  - Grant Files, 1985-1995; 1.5
    - American Conservation Association Projects, 1986- (Box 77)
    - Acid Rain, 1986 (Box 77)
    - Billboards, 1986 (Box 77)
    - Land Use, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Environmental Assessment Council, 1986 (Box 77)
    - Environmental Bond Issue, 1986 (Box 77)
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 77)
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Youth employment program, 1989 (Box 77)
    - Conservation of Outdoor Settings Project & Book (Box 77)
    - Report on Hazardous Waste regrant Conservation Foundation (Box 77)
    - Project for research experimentation, and application in outdoor bronze statuary cleaning, preservation and restoration, 1988 (Box 77)
    - World Monuments Fund (Box 77)
    - Nancy Hank Memorial Project, 1984 (Box 77)
    - Wirth Medal (father and son) National Park Foundation, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Environmental Task Force (President Reagan), 1981 (Box 77)
    - Caribbean Study (Carlozzi), 1976 (Box 77)
    - Natural Area Council, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Natural Heritage Trust, 1974 (Box 77)
    - Follow up on President's Commission on American Outdoors, 1987 (Box 77)
    - Alaska II, 1990-1992 (Box 77)
    - Commission on the Adirondack, 1991 (Box 77)
    - Celebration of the Outdoors/Land Water Fund/Conservation Foundation, 1990 (Box 77)
    - Land & Water Fund, 1991-1995 (Box 77)
    - Environmental Bond Act, 1990 (Box 77)
    - American Horizons, 2 folders/ (Box 77)
      Re: Population
    - Paul Maze Book, 1985 (Box 77)
  - Grant Files, 1992-1996; 1.6
    - The Adirondack Council, 2 folders. (Box 85)
    - Adirondack Nature Conservancy and Adirondack Land Trust (Box 85)
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation (Box 85)
    - American Farmland Trust (Box 85)
    - American Rivers (Box 85)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 85)
    - Association for the Protection of the Adirondacks (Box 85)
    - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 85)
    - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Jnc. (Box 85)
    - Children's Earth Fund, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Kids World Council, 1993 April (Box 86)
    - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1992 (Box 86)
    - L.R. Travel Materials Earth Summit - Rio de Janeiro, 1992 (Box 86)
    - United Nations Conference on Environment and Development, Rio de Janeiro (Earth Summit), 1992 (Box 86)
    - Coast Alliance, 2 folders. (Box 86)
    - Coast Alliance, 5 folders. (Box 87)
    - The Conservation Fund (Box 87)
    - Conservation Jntemational (Box 87)
    - Conservation Law Foundation of New England, Inc. (Box 87)
    - Finances (Box 87)
    - Friends of the Earth (Box 87)
    - Green Seal (Box 88)
    - Inform, 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Land Trust Alliance, 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Land and Water Fund (Box 88)
    - League Conservation Voters Education Fund (Box 88)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 88)
    - Meetings, 1994 (Box 88)
    - Meetings, 1993 (Box 88)
    - Meetings, 1992 (Box 88)
    - Meetings, 1992 (Box 89)
    - Mineral Policy Center, 3 folders. (Box 89)
    - New York Zoological Society (The Wildlife Conservation Society) (Box 89)
    - National Audubon Society, 3 folders. (Box 89)
    - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation (Box 89)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association (Box 90)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 90)
    - National Wildflower Research Center (Box 90)
    - National Wildlife Federation (Box 90)
    - National Resources Defense Council (Box 90)
    - Nature Conservancy (Box 90)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund (Box 90)
    - New York Environmental Institute (Box 90)
    - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 2 folders. (Box 90)
    - New York Zoological Society (Box 90)
    - Northern Rockies Action Group (Box 90)
    - 1000 Friends of Florida (Box 90)
    - 1000 Friends of Oregon (Box 90)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 91)
    - Planet Live: countdown 2000, Inc. (Box 91)
    - Projects: Costa Rica (Box 91)
    - Publicly Owned Bronze Sculpture in Outdoor Setting (Report), 1985-1989; 3 folders. (Box 91)
    - Project for Public Spaces, Inc. (Box 91)
    - Rails to Trails Conservancy (Box 91)
    - Review and Planning Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 92)
    - Scenic America, 2 folders. (Box 92)
    - Scenic Hudson, 2 folders. (Box 92)
    - Shawangunk Conservancy, Inc. (Box 92)
    - Sierra Club Foundation, 2 folders. (Box 92)
    - Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund (Box 92)
    - Snake River Institute (Box 92)
    - Southeast Alaska Conservation Council (Box 92)
    - Southern Environmental Law Center (Box 92)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 October 10 (Box 92)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 October 7 (Box 92)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 October 5 (Box 92)
    - 40th Anniversary Report, 1999 November (Box 92)
    - The Trust for Public Land (Box 93)
    - Trustees for Alaska (Box 93)
    - Vermont Natural Resources Council (Box 93)
    - Wave Hill (Box 93)
    - Wilderness Society (Box 93)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 93)
    - World Wildlife Fund/The Conservation Foundation (Box 93)
    - Wyoming Outdoor Council (Box 93)
    - Grants - A-E (Box 94)
    - Grants - F-H (Box 94)
    - Grants - I-N (Box 94)
    - Grants - O-Z (Box 94)
    - Applicants - A-Z (Box 94)
    - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 94)
  - Grant Files, 1996; 1.7
    - Children's Earth Fund - African Medical & Research Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - "Children Light the Way", 1991 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Waste Management of North America "Earth Rangers" (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - LOGO Mr. Robert J. Morris, 1994 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Save the Rainforest - Bruce Calhoun, 1991 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Renew America - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - EDEA - Children to Children Energy Bridge, 1991 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Global Action Plan, 1993 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Kids for Saving Earth, 1993 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Trickle Up Program, Inc., 1991-1994 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - P3 Foundation, 1991 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Solar Box Cookers International, 1991-1993 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Solar Box Cookers Demo, 1994 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund - Solar Box Cookers International Network Project, 1994 (Box 82)
    - Children's Earth Fund Project, 1995 (Box 82)
    - Adirondack Council (Box 83)
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation American (Box 83)
    - American Rivers (Box 83)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 83)
    - Catskill Center for Conservation and Development Inc. Coast Alliance (Box 83)
    - Coast Alliance (Box 83)
    - Conservation Fund (Box 83)
    - Conservation Law Foundation (Box 83)
    - Environmental Advocates (Box 83)
      formerly NY Environmental Institute
    - Friends of the Earth (Box 83)
    - Inform (Box 83)
    - Land Trust Alliance (Box 83)
    - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund (Box 83)
    - Mineral Policy Center (Box 83)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 83)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association Inc. (Box 83)
    - National Wildflower Research Center (Box 83)
    - National Wildlife Federation (Box 83)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 83)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund (Box 83)
    - New York Parks Conservation Association (Box 83)
    - NYZS/Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 83)
      formerly New York Zoological Society.
    - Open Space Institute (Box 83)
    - Project for Public Spaces Inc. (Box 83)
    - Rails to Trails Conservancy (Box 83)
    - Scenic America (Box 83)
    - Scenic Hudson Inc. (Box 83)
    - Sierra Club Foundation (Box 83)
    - Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund (Box 83)
    - Southern Environmental Law Center (Box 83)
    - Southeast Alaska Conservation Council (Box 83)
    - Student Conservation Association (Box 83)
    - Trust for Public Land (Box 83)
    - Trustees for Alaska (Box 83)
    - Vermont Natural Resources Council (Box 83)
    - Wilderness Society (Box 83)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 83)
    - World Wildlife Fund/ Conservation Foundation Land & Water Fund Project (Box 83)
    - Children's Earth Fund Project (Box 83)
      additional $35,000 XC 1996 March 4
    - Mothers and others additional (Box 83)
  - Grant Files, 1997; 1.8
    - Declinations, 1997 (Box 84)
      e grants not approved at Board Meeting, 1996 October 18
    - Adirondack Council (Box 84)
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation (Box 84)
    - Alaska Fund for the Future (Box 84)
    - American Rivers (Box 84)
    - Andrus Center for Public Policy (Box 84)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 84)
    - Catskill Center (Box 84)
    - Coast Alliance (Box 84)
    - Conservation Fund (Box 84)
    - Conservation International (Box 84)
    - Conservation Law Foundation (Box 84)
    - Earthjustice Legal Defense Fund (Box 84)
      formerly Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund
    - Environmental Advocates (Box 84)
      formerly New York Environmental Institute
    - Friends of the Earth (Box 84)
    - Land Trust Alliance (Box 84)
    - LCV Education Fund (Box 84)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 84)
    - Mineral Policy Center (Box 84)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 84)
    - National Parks and Conservation (Box 84)
    - National Wildflower Research Center (Lady Bird Johnson Research Center) (Box 84)
    - National Wildlife Federation (NWF) (Box 84)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 84)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund (Box 84)
    - New York Parks and Conservation (Box 84)
    - New York Zoological Society (The Wildlife Conservation Society) (Box 84)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 84)
    - Project for Public Spaces and Health Policy (Box 84)
    - Rails to Trails Conservancy (Box 84)
    - Scenic America (Box 84)
    - Scenic Hudson (Box 84)
    - SE Alaska Conservation Council (Box 84)
    - Trust for Public Land (Box 84)
    - The Wilderness Society (Box 84)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 84)
    - World Wildlife Fund (Box 84)
    - Projects: Mothers and Others (Box 84)
    - Projects: Renewable Energy (Box 84)
    - Projects: Urban Project (Box 84)
  - Grant Files, 1998; 1.9
    - Adirondack Council (Box 84)
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation (Box 84)
    - Alaska Fund for the Future American Rivers (Box 84)
    - American Rivers (Box 84)
    - Andrus Center for Public Policy (Box 84)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 84)
    - Catskill Center (Box 84)
    - Coast Alliance (Box 84)
    - Conservation Fund (Box 84)
    - Conservation International (Box 84)
    - Conservation Law Foundation (Box 84)
    - Earthjustice Legal Defense Fund (Box 84)
    - Friends of the Earth (Box 84)
    - Land Trust Alliance (Box 84)
    - LCV Education Fund (Box 84)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 84)
    - Mineral Policy Center (Box 84)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 84)
    - National Parks and Conservation (Box 84)
    - National Wildflower Research Center (Lady Bird Johnson Research Center) (Box 84)
    - National Wildlife Federation (NWF) (Box 84)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 84)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund (Box 84)
    - New York Parks and Conservation (Box 84)
    - New York Zoological Society (The Wildlife Conservation Society) (Box 84)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 84)
    - Project for Public Spaces (Box 84)
    - Public Voice for Food and Health Policy (Box 84)
    - Rails to Trails Conservancy (Box 84)
    - Riverwatch Network (Box 84)
    - Scenic America (Box 84)
    - Scenic Hudson (Box 84)
    - SE Alaska Conservation Council (Box 84)
    - Trust for Public Land (Box 84)
    - The Wilderness Society (Box 84)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 84)
    - World Wildlife Fund (WWF) (Box 84)
    - American for our Heritage Project, 1998 (Box 100)
    - Wise Use Project, 1995 (Box 100)
    - League of Conservation Voters Project, 1995 (Box 100)
    - John Nettleton-Cornell University Project, 1995 (Box 100)
    - Urban Project, 1993 (Box 100)
  - Grant Files, 1999; 1.10
    Conditions Governing Access
    Records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Entire file open in 2015. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted from scholarly access.
    - Mineral Policy Center, 1999 (Box 95)
    - National Audubon Society, 1999 (Box 95)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1999 (Box 95)
    - National Resources Defense Council, 1999 (Box 95)
    - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Ladybird Johnson Wildflower Center (Formerly NWRC), 1999 (Box 95)
      formerly NWRC.
    - National Wildlife Research Center, 1999 (Box 95)
    - New Yark Conservation Education Fund, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Wildlife Conservation Society, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Pace University re: Pace Environmental Law Center, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Open Space Institute, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Project for Public Spaces, Inc., 1999 (Box 95)
    - Rails-to-Trails re: Second International Conference, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Scenic America, Inc., 1999 (Box 95)
    - Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund, Inc., 1999 (Box 95)
    - Southeast Alaska Conservation Council, 1999 (Box 95)
    - The Trust for Public Land, 1999 (Box 95)
    - The Wilderness Society, 1999 (Box 95)
    - World Wildlife Fund, 1999 (Box 95)
    - World Resources Institute, 1999 (Box 95)
    - Alaska Project, 1999 (Box 95)
  - Grant Files, 2000; 1.11
    Grant records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire File open in 2016. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted.
    - Adirondack Council (Box 99)
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation (Box 99)
    - Alaska Fund for the Future (Box 99)
    - American Farmland Trust (Box 99)
    - American Rivers (Box 99)
    - Appalachian Mountain Club (Box 99)
    - The Catskill Center for Conservation (Box 99)
    - Coast Alliance (Box 99)
    - The Conservation Fund: Land Work in Vermont Land and Water Fund (Box 99)
    - Conservation International (Box 99)
    - Conservation Law Foundation (Box 99)
    - Earth Day Network (Box 99)
    - Earth Justice Legal Defense Fund (Box 99)
    - Environmental Advocates (Box 99)
    - Friends of the Earth (Box 99)
    - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center (Box 99)
    - Land Trust Alliance (Box 99)
    - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund (Box 99)
    - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 99)
    - Mineral Policy Center (Box 99)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 99)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association (Box 99)
    - National Wildlife Federation (Box 99)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 99)
    - The Nature Conservancy (Box 99)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund (Box 99)
    - New York Parks and Conservation Association (Box 99)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 99)
    - Project for Public Spaces (Box 99)
    - The Trust for Public Land (Box 99)
    - The Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 99)
    - Rails to Trails (Box 99)
    - River Watch Network (Box 99)
    - Scenic America (Box 99)
    - Scenic Hudson (Box 99)
    - SE Alaska Conservation Council (Box 99)
    - Sierra Club Foundation (Box 99)
    - The Trust for Public Land (Box 99)
    - The Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 99)
    - The Wilderness Society (Box 99)
    - World Resources Institute (Box 99)
    - World Wildlife Fund Conservation Foundation (Box 99)
    - Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet Project (Box 99)
    - Land and Water Conservation Fund Project (Box 99)
    - New York Environmental Project (Box 99)
  - Grant Files, 2001; 1.12
    Records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Entire file open in 2017. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricted from scholarly access.
    - Adirondack Council (Box 98)
      Grant records more than 15 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire File open in 2017. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours. Records which document the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family are restricte
    - Alaska Conservation Foundation (Box 98)
    - Brennan Center for Justice at NY School of Law (Box 98)
    - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development (Box 98)
    - Coast Alliance (Box 98)
    - The Conservation Fund (Box 98)
    - Conservation International (Box 98)
    - Defenders/ The Endangered Species Coalition (Box 98)
    - Earthjustice Legal Defense Fund 2003 (Box 98)
    - Environmental Advocates (Box 98)
    - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center (Box 98)
      formerly National Wildflower Research Center
    - Land Trust Alliance (Box 98)
    - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund (Box 98)
    - National Audubon Society (Box 98)
    - National Parks and Conservation Association (Box 98)
    - New York Parks and Conservation Association (Box 98)
    - National Wildlife Federation (Box 98)
    - Natural History Museum of the Adirondacks (Box 98)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 98)
    - New York Conservation Education Fund (Box 98)
    - New York Parks and Conservation (Box 98)
    - Open Space Institute (Box 98)
    - Project for Public Spaces (Box 98)
    - Rails to Trails (Box 98)
    - INC. REP Environmental Education Foundation (Box 98)
    - River Network (Box 98)
    - Rocky Mountain Institute (Box 98)
    - Scenic America (Box 98)
    - Scenic Hudson (Box 98)
    - SE Alaska Conservation Council (Box 98)